Guide to the Cornell University Olin, Kroch, Uris Libraries' administrative records, 1961-2003.
Cornell University Olin, Kroch, Uris Libraries' administrative records, 1961-2003
- Series XIII: Patron Services
  - 26N. Patron Services -General
    - 26.N.4 Bear Access Services, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - 26.N.5 Censorship Issues--CUL, 1987-88 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - 26.N.10 Censorship Issues--General, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - 26.N.15 Com. Doc. Delivery Report (1994), 1994-95 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - 26.N.20 Computerized Reference Service, 1981-1988 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - 26.N.25 Copyright Issues, 1990-91, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - 26.N.30 Electronic Reserve, 1994-98 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - 26.N.35 Electronic Text Center, 1996-99 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - 26.N.36 ETC--Full-Text Databases, 1998, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - 26.N.40 Optical Disk Technology, 1985, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - 26.N.42 Humanities Symposia (1997/98), 1997-98 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - 26.N.45 NEXIS, 194-85, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - 26.N.50 Optical Disk Technology, 1983-84, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - 26.N.55 Photocopy Services, 1982-95 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - 26.N.65 Telefacsimile Projects, 1984, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - 26P. Services Issues
    - 26.P.5 Building & Service Hours--Olin, 1983-84, 1988-93, 1997-99 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - 26.P.10 Building & Service Hours--Uris, 1993-94, 1997, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - 26.P.15 Hours Reduction Debate (1993), 1992-93 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - 26.P.20 Hours Reduction Summary (1992-94), 1992-95 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - 26.P.25 LibQual Project (2001-), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - 26.P.50 Uris-24hr Study, 1982-1996 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - 26.P.51 Uris - Extended Hours, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - 26R. Special Collections
    - 6.R.20 ILL Guidelines--Special Coll., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - 26.R.30 Policies--CUL--Special Coll., 1986, 1994, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - 26T. Stack Access - Olin
    - 26.T. Stack Access (1961-86), 1961-86 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - 26.T. Stack Access (1987), 1987 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - 26.T. Stack Access (1992-93), 1992-93 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Series XIV: Personnel
  - 28H. Personnel Issues - General
    - 28.H.10 Classification Review (1989-91), 1989-91 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - 28.H.12 Classifications Review (1992-93), 1992-93 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - 28.H.15 Compensation, 1988-91 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - 28.H.17 Continuing Education, 1997, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - 28.H.20 Employee Service Awards, 1954, 1958, 1963-64, 1969, 1973-74, 1985-89, 1991-00 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - 28.H.30 Hiring Freeze (1990-91), 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - 28.H.31 Hiring Freeze (2001-02), 2001-02 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - 28.H.35 Interviewing Procedures/Techniques, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - 28.H.40 Job Classifications, 1981-82, 1988-89, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - 28.H.45 Leadership Training, 1995-96 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - 28.H.50 Orientation, 1979, 1982-1984, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Human Resources-Information for New Employees, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 35A)
    - 28.H.55 Sexual Harassment, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - 28.H.57 Sick Room (Olin), 1997 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - 28.H.60 Staffing Levels, 1984, 1988-89, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - 28.H.63 Staff Recognition Program, 1999-01 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - 28.H.65 Staff Survey (1987), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - 28.H.70 Student Employee Recognition, 1995, 1997-98, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - 28.H.75 Support Staff Development Committee, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - 28.H.80 Training Guidelines, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - 28.H.90 Volunteers, 1997, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - 28K. Personnel Policies - CUL
    - 28.K.20 Emergency Closings, 1986, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - 28.K.30 Performance Dialogue/Appraisal Information, 1981, 1983, 1988, 1992-93 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - 28.K.35 Personnel Policies--Exempt, 1984-86, 1990, 1992, 1995, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - 28.K.40 Personnel Policies--Non-Exempt, 1981, 1984, 1989, 1993, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - 28.K.45 Student Employees, 1984-86, 1988, 1990-92 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - 28N. Personnel Searches
    - 28.N.62 Wason Search--Curator (2000), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - 28.N.64 Southeast Asia Librarian (2000), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - 28.N.66 Southeast Asia Librarian (2001), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - 28.N.68 Fine Arts Search (2000), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - 28.N.72 Fine Arts Search (2001), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 28.N.74 Reference Search (2001), 2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 28.N.76 Africana Librarian Search (2001), 1992, 1999, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 28.N.70 Reference Search (2000-2001), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 28.P.20 Justifications (1998), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 28.P.20 Justifications (1999), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 28.P.20 Justifications (2000), 2000 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 28.P.20 Justifications (2001), 2001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Series XV. Physical Plant
  - 30A. Annex Library
    - 30.A.10 Annex Library--Construction (1997/98), 1997/98 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - 30.A.25 Maintenance Issues, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 20B. Environmental Conditions
    - 30.B.5 Asbestos Removal, 1984, 1987-88, 1993-94 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - 30.B.6 Asbestos Removal (Olin)--1997, 1988, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - 30.B.10 Environmental Health--General, 1984-85, 1987, 1993, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - 30.B.15 Environmental--Misc., 1983, 1985, 1987, 1996, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - 30.B.20 Environmental/Security--Special Collection, 1987, 1989-91 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - 30.B.25 Lighting--Environmental Aspects, 1983, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 30F. Maintenance Management
    - 30.F.5 Maintenance Management--General, 1984, 1990, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - 30.F.10 Maintenance Management--Priorities, 1987-90, 1992, 1994-96, 1998, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - 30H. Physical Plant - General
    - 30.H.5 ADA Issues, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - 30.H.10 Archived Drawings, 1994-95 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - 30.H.20 Building Coordinator, 1992-93 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - 30.H.30 Custodial Services, 1970-71, 1974-77, 1979, 1983-86, 1988, 1990-91, 1993, 1998, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - 30.H.40 Floor Plans, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - 30.H.50 Inventory Equipment, 1984, 1987, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - 30.H.70 Telephones & Intercoms, 1984-85, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - 30J. Physical Plant - Kroch
    - 30.J.10 Emergency Systems, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - 30.J.12 Environmental Systems, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - 30.J.15 Exhibit Cases, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - 30.J.20 Lighting, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - 30.J.22 Miscellaneous--Kroch, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - 30.J.25 Severinghaus Reading Room, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - 30.J.30 Shelving, 1995-97 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - 30.J.35 Skylights (Kroch), 1994-96, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - 30.J.40 Sprinklers (Kroch), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - 30L. Physical Plant - Olin
    - 30.L.5 Book Returns, 1966-67 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - 30.L.8 HVAC System--Complaints, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - 30.L.10 HVAC System--Olin--General, 1983-86, 1991, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - 30.L.12 HVAC System--SBRA Estimate (1992), 1992 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - 30.L.15 Lighting--Olin--General, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - 30.L.20 Maintenance Problems--Olin, 1984-85, 1987-88, 1990-91, 1993, 1995-96 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - 30.L.25 Mech. Systems--Lacey Report (1984), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - 30.L.26 Mech. Systems--Lull Report (1991), 1991 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - 30.L.30 Signs--Olin, 1980, 1985, 1989-90, 1993, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - 30.L.35 Sprinkler System--General (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - 30.L.37 Sprinkler Syst.--SBRA Estimate (1992), 1992 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - 30.L.40 Structural Considerations--Olin, 1980, 1984-86, 1988-89 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - 30.L.42 Terrace, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - 30.L.45 Utilities, 1985-86 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - 30.L.50 Water Leaks, 1976, 1980, 1982, 1984-87 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - 30N. Physical Plant - Uris
    - 30.N Physical Plant-URIS (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 30.N.5 Elevators, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 30.N.7 Environmental Issues, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 30.N.10 Furniture, 1995-97 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 30.N.40 Stack Renovation Study (1990), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 30.N.60 White Library, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 30R. Renovations and Remodeling - CUL
    - 30.P Ren & Remodeling-CUL (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 30.P.20 Lull Report--ILR (1990), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 30Q. Renovations and Remodeling - Kroch
    - 30.Q Ren. & Remodeling- Kroch (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - 30.Q.5 Consulting Stamps, 1994, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - 30.Q.10 Exhibition Cases, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - 30.Q.25 Severing haus Reading Room, 2000-01 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - 30.Q.30 Skylight (1995-97), 1995-97 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 30R. Renovations and Remodeling - Olin
    - 30.R Ren. & Remodeling- Olin (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - 30.R.2 Basement Reorganization (1983), 1983 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - 30.R.4 Front Entrance Redesign, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - 30.R.6 Bindery Remodeling (1984-85), 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - 30.R.8 Catalog Maint. Remodeling (1984-85), 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - 30.R.10 Current Periodical Room Reorganization (1985), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - 30.R.12 Microformat Storage Redesign (1985), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - 30.R.14 Shelving Added--Compact (1985), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - 30.R.16 Shelving Added--Conventional (1985-86), 1985-86 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - 30.R.18 Development Office Remodeling (1986), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - 30.R.20 Eighth Floor Addition (1986-87), 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - 30.R.22 Lower Level Renovations (1987-89), 1987-89 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - 30.R.24 Robison Conference Room (1987), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - 30.R.26 Wason/Echols Expansion (1987), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - 30.R.28 Second Floor Renovations (1988-89), 1988-89 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - 30.R.30 Staff Lounge Renovations (1988-89), 1988-89 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - 30.R.32 Shelving Added--Compact (1988-89), 1988-89 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - 30.R.34 Photocopy Renovations (1990), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - 30.R.36 Shelving Added--Compact (1990), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - 30.R.38 Shelving Added--Compact (1991), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - 30.R.40 Roof and Front Entrance (1993), 1993 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - 30.R.42 HVAC Renovations (1995- ), 1995-96 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - 30.R.43 Information Kiosks (1995- ), 1995, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - 30.R.44 Lower Level Renovations (1995), 1994-95 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - 30.R.46 Room 106 Renovations (1995), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - 30.R.48 Window Replacement (1996), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - 30.R.49 Sign Project (1996- ), 1996-98 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - 30.R.50 Electronic Text Center (1996), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - 30.R.52 ILS Renovation (1998), 1998 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - 30.R.54 CTS Workstation Project (1998), 1998 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - 30.R.56 Wireless Computing (2000- ), 2000-01 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - 30.R.58 Libe Cafe (2000-01), 2000-01 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - 30.R.60 First Floor (2000- ), 2000-01 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - 30S. Renovations and Remodeling - Uris
    - 30.S.2 Uris Circulation Area (1981-82), 1981-82 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - 30.S.5 Media Room Renovation Proj. (1989-90), 1989-90 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - 30.S.10 Electronic Classroom (1994-95), 1994-95 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - 30.S.15 HVAC Renovations (1994-96), 1994-96 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - 30.S.18 FABIT-Uris (1998-2000), 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - 30.S.20 Creation Station Project (1999-2000), 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - 30T. Shelving - General
    - 30.T Shelving-General (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - 30.T.5 Compact Shelving--Fire Safety, 1979, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - 30.T.10 Compact Shelving--General, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - 30.T.15 Compact Shelving--Library Technology Report (1990), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - 30.T.20 Conventional Shelving--General, 1985, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - 30.T.25 Shelving & User Seats statistics, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - 30V. Space Issues - Misc.
    - 30.V Space Issues- Misc. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 30.V.5 Space Issues--Kroch (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 30.V.10 Space Issues--Olin, 1984-87, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - 30.V.15 Space Issues--Uris, 1977-1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Series XVI: Planning
  - 32A. Annex - Expansion Planning (1986-1990)
    - 32. Planning (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 32.A Annex-Expan. PLNG (1986-90), 1986-90 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 32.A.5 Addition --Planning (1989-90), 1989-90 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 32.A.10 Expansion Planning--Annex Study (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 32.A.15 Annex Expansion Comm--General, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 32.A.20 Annex Expansion Comm--Minutes, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 32.A.25 Annex Expansion Comm--Report, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 32.A.30 Storage Needs Survey (1986), 1986 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 32.A.35 Storage Needs Survey (1990), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 32B. Annex - Expansion Planning (1994-)
    - 32.B Annex Expan. PLNG (1994- ), 1994- (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - 32.B.5 Administrative Taskforce (1994), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - 32.B.10 Dill Report (1995), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - 32.B.30 Offsite Selection--Asia, 1994, 1996-97 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - 32.B.40 Offsite Selection--Olin, 1995-97 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - 32.B.45 Public Relations, 1991, 1994-95 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - 32.B.50 Shelf Measurement Project (1994), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - 32C. Expansion Planning - Elsewhere
    - 32.C Expan. PLNG-Elsewhere (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - 32.C.5 Compact Storage--Other Institutions, 1978, 1985-86, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - 32.C.10 Expansion--Other Institutions, 1981, 1985, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - 32.C.15 Northwestern--Compact Shelving, 1983, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - 32.C.20 Remote Storage, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - 32E. Expansion Planning - (pre-Kroch)
    - 32.E Expan. PLNG (Pre-Kroch) (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - 32.E.5 Frantz Proposal (1985), 1985 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - 32.E.10 MIRA Study (1982-83), 1982-83 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - 32.E.15 Olin Internal Pruposals (1979), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - 32.E.20 Olin Internal Space Study (1981/1983), 1981/1983 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - 32.E.25 Space Projections (1963), 1963 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - 32.E.30 Wujcik Thesis--Spacial Collections (1984), 1984 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - 32G. Kroch Planning - General (1987-91)
    - 32.G Kroch PLNG-Gen. (1989-91), 1989-91 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - 32.G.5 Administrative Correspondence, 1986-91 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - 32.G.10 General Information, 1985, 1987, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - 32.G.15 General Planning Meetings, 1985, 1987- 89 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - 32.G.20 Presentations--Expansion, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - 32H. Kroch Planning - SBRA (1987-88)
    - 32.H Kroch PLNG-SBRA (1987-88), 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - 32.H.5 Drawings in Archives, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - 32.H.10 SBRA--Correspondence & Meetings, 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - 32.H.20 SBRA--General, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - 32J. Kroch Planning - Site Options (1987-88)
    - 32.I Kroch PLNG- Site Options (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - 32.J.5 Day Hall Site (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - 32.J.10 Drawings (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - 32.J.15 Non-Contiguous Options, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - 32.J.20 Stimson Meadow Site, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - 32K. Kroch Planning - Space Program (1987-88)
    - 32.K Kroch PLNG-Space PROG. (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - 32.K.20 SBRA--Space Program Data, 1987-88, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - 32.K.15 Space Program--Drafts 1.0-2.0, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - 32.K.20 Space Program--Drafts 3.0-3.2, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - 32.K.25 Space Program--Drafts 4.0-4.1, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - 32.L Kroch Renovation PLAN (1992- ), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 32.L.5 "Action List" (1994), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 32.L.20 Miscellaneous Planning, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 32.L.25 Olin/Kroch Corridor, 1994-95 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 32M. Library Facilities Planning Committee - (1986-89)
    - 32.M LIB. FAC. Planning Comm. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 32.M.5 Library Facilities Planning Committee--General (1986-89), 1986-89 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 32.M.10 Library Facilities Planning Committee--Minutes (1986-89), 1986-89 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - 32.M.15 Library Facilities Planning Committee--Olin Data, 1985-86 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - 32.M.20 Mann Library Expansion, 1983, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - 32.M.25 Vet Library Expansion, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 32P. Off-Site Facility
    - 32.P Off-Site Facility (1994- ), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - 32.P.10 Off-Site Facilities--Elsewhere, 1992-94 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - 32.P.15 Off-Site--Facilities Subcommittee, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - 32.P.20 Off-Site Planning--General, 1990-91, 1993-95, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - 32.P.5 Dill Report (1995), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - 32.P.25 Off-Site--Selection Subcommittee, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - 32.P.30 Off-Site Taskforce Report (1992), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - 32.P.35 Selection of Materials (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - 32.N.10 Off-Site Facility (1977-78), 1977-78 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - 32.N.30 Off-Site Facility (1977-78), 1977-78 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - 32.N.15 Off-Site Facility (1977-78), 1977-78 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 32Q. Olin Renovation Planning (1991-)
    - 32.Q Olin Ren. Planning (1991- ), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - 32.Q.5 Code Issues, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - 32.Q.10 General Planning (1990-91), 1990-91 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - 32.Q.15 General Planning (1992-93), 1992-93 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - 32.Q.20 General Planning (1994-95), 1994-95 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - 32.Q.21 General Planning (1996- ), 1996-2001 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - 32.Q.23 Lower Level Study (1994), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - 32.Q.25 Lull Report (1991), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - 32.Q.30 Mechanical Issues, 1991-92, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - 32.Q.32 Olin/Uris "Connector", 1994-95 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - 32.Q.35 Space Program--Conservation, 1988-92 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - 32.Q.33 Olin/Uris "Plaza", 1994-97, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - 32.Q.40 Space Program--General, 1988-89, 1991-92 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - 32.Q.45 Space Program--Public Services, 1990-92 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - 32.Q. 50 Space Program--Special Needs, 1990-91 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - 32R. Planning, Long-Term (pre-1980)
    - 32.R Planning Long-Term (Pre-1980), 1980-Pre. (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - 32.R.5 General Planning (1975-80), 1975-80 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - 32.R.10 Mineka Committee Report (1971), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - 32.R.15 Library Self-Study Report (1975), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - 32.R.20 Library Task Force Report (1975), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - 32S. Planning, Long-Term (1980-1989)
    - 32.S PLNG. Long-Term (1980-89), 1980-89 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - 32.S.5 Annex Facility (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - 32.S.10 CUL Planning Statements, 1980, 1985-88 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - 32.S.15 Institutional Planning Study (1990), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - 32.S.20 Planning Project (1985-86), 1985-86 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - 32.S.25 Priorities and Planning--CUL, 1983-89 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - 32.S.30 Priorities and Planning--Cornell--General, 1983-85, 1989-92, 1994-95, 1998-99 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - 32T. Planning - Long Term (1990-1999)
    - 32.T PLNG. Long Term (1990-99), 1990-99 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - 32.T.10 Priorities & Planning--Cornell-General (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - 32.R.20 Tactical Plan (1998-99), 1998-99 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - 32.T.20 Priorities & Planning-CUL-General, 1992, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - 32.T.25 Electronic Publishing, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - 32.T.27 Humanities Report (Cornell, 1998), 1998 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - 32.T.30 Medical Library Cooperation (1998), 1998 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - 32.T.32 NEH Regional Humanities Center (1999), 1999 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - 32U. Planning, Short Term (1997-)
    - 32.U PLNG. Long Term (2000- ), 2000 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - 32.U.10 Digital Features Plan (2000-02), 2000-02 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - 32.U.15 Master Plan (2002-07), 2002-07 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - 32.U.25 Library Focus Group (2000), 2000 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - 32.U.30 North Campus Iniatives (1998- ), 1998 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - 32.U.35 Olin/Uris Working Group (2001/02), 2001/02 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - 32.U.50 West Campus Iniatives (1999- ), 1999-02 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - 32V. Strategic Plan - Cornell (1994)
    - 32.V Strategic Plan--CU (1994), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 32.V.5 Academic Leadership Seminar (1995), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 32.V.30 Library Response, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 32.V.70 Task Force Reports (1994), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 32X. Uris Renovation Planning (1993-)
    - 32.W.10 Additional Planning--General (1979-80), 1979-80 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 32.X Uris Ren. Planning (1993- ), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 32.X.5 Building Entry, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 32.X.15 General Planning (1993- ), 1993-99 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 32.X.20 Expansion (1998), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 32.X.21 Expansion (1999), 1999 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 32.X.30 Media Services, 1980, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - 32.X.40 SBRA Involvement (1999), 1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Series XVII: Publications
  - 33D. Donor Related
    - 33 Publications (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - 33.D Donor Related (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - 32.D.5 Far Above, 1992-96 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 32P. Patron Oriented
    - 33.P Patron Oriented (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - 33.P.5 Cyte & Byte, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 32S. Staff Oriented
    - 33.S Staff Oriented (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - 33.S.5 Kaleidoscope--Vol. 1, 1992-93 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - 33.S.5 Kaleidoscope --Vol. 2, 1993-94 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - 33.S.5 Kaleidocope--Vol. 3, 1994-95 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - 33.S.5 Kaleidocope--Vol. 4, 1995-96 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - 33.S.5 Kaleidocope--Vol. 5, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - 33.S.5 Kaleidoscope-Vol. 6, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - 33.S.5 Kaleidocope--Vol. 7, 1999-00 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - 33.S.5 Kaleidocope--Vol. 8, 1999-00 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - 33.S.5 Kaleidocope--Vol. 9, 2000-01 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - 33.S.5 Kaleidocope--Vol. 10, 2001-02 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Series XVIII: Security and Safety
  - 34E. Emergency Preparedness
    - 34.Security & Safety (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - 34.E Emergency Preparedness (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - 34.E.1 General, 1978, 1983, 1990, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - 34.E.5 Closing Procedure, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - 34.E.10 Evacuation Procedures--Olin, 1994, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - 34.E.15 Departmental Safety Representatives, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - 34.E.20 Emergency Call List, 1997-98 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - 34.E.25 Evacuation Procedures--Olin, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - 34.E.30 Evacuation Procedures--Uris, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - 34.E.35 Fire Marshals & Procedures--OKU, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - 34.E.40 Inclement Weather Policy, 1984, 1986-87, 1991-93, 1995-96, 2000-01 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - 34.E.45 Insurance Coverage, 1982, 1990, 1993-94 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - 34.E.60 Personnel Crisis Aissistance, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - 34.E.65 Risk Management--General, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - 34.E.70 Safety Officer--OKU, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - 32F. Fire Protection
    - 34.F Fire Protection (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - 34.F.5 Arkwright Report--Olin (1996), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - 34.F.15 Fire Watch Requirements (Box 15, Folder 46)